okay folks let's take a look at some
好吧，我们来看看一些
data now on mixed strategies and begin
现在就采用混合策略并开始
to see whether or not some of the
看看是否有一些
subtleties that we were talking about
我们正在谈论的微妙之处
earlier actually play play themselves
早先实际上玩自己玩
out in real incarnations of these games
这些游戏的真实化身
so in particular we mentioned that mixed
所以我们特别提到
strategy Nash equilibria can have some
策略纳什均衡可以有一些
counterintuitive features and there can
违反直觉的功能，并且可以
be can be somewhat subtle to solve for
解决可能会有些微妙
so we might wonder whether people
所以我们可能想知道人们是否
actually really obey the predictions of
实际上真的服从于
Nash equilibrium in these settings so
在这些情况下纳什均衡
let's have a look at professional soccer
让我们来看看职业足球
penalty kicks and we'll look at some
点球大战，我们来看一些
data that was gathered by Ignacio
Ignacio收集的数据
Palacios Huerta in 2003 where what he
Palacios Huerta在2003年
did was he actually looked at as a whole
是他实际上从整体上看
series of FIFA games that he recorded
他录制的一系列FIFA游戏
off of television different different
电视不同
shows he looked at fourteen hundred and
显示他看了一千四百
seventeen penalty kicks and in the
十七次罚球并在
Spanish league England in Italy and so
西班牙联赛英格兰在意大利等
forth and so he's looking at at high
来，所以他看着高
level soccer and looked at penalty kicks
水平足球，看着罚球
and what he did is he kept track of
他所做的是他一直在追踪
whether people kicked to the left they
人们是否向左踢
kicked to the center they kicked to the
踢到他们踢到的中心
right and whether they were using their
对以及他们是否正在使用他们的
left leg or the right leg and and we're
左腿还是右腿，而我们
gonna look just at this simplified
会看看这个简化的
version that corresponds to what we
对应于我们的版本
analysed earlier which is just a left
前面分析过的只是剩下的
kick right kick and the goalie can
踢右脚踢，守门员可以
either move left to right which he
要么左右移动
actually analyzes a subset of the data
实际分析数据的子集
on page 402 and will look at what data
在第402页，将查看哪些数据
he actually has and from that paper
他实际上有
okay so here's based on on what he finds
好吧，这是根据他的发现
out of these fourteen hundred and
在这1400个中
seventeen penalty kicks these are sort
这些罚球有十七个
of the averages so in situations where
平均值的情况下，
kickers go left and goalies go left
踢脚向左走，守门员向左走
kickers win fifty eight point percent of
踢球者赢得百分之五十八
the time goalies win forty-two percent
守门员的时间赢了42％
of the time in situations where the
在这种情况下
kicker goes left and a goalie goes right
踢脚向左走，守门员向右走
then the the kicker wins ninety five
然后踢手赢得九十五
percent of the time if the kicker goes
踢球走时的百分比
right and that go he goes left they went
对，他走了，他走了，他们走了
the kicker wins ninety three percent of
踢手赢得百分之九十三
the time and so
时间等等
so so these are the actual numbers that
所以这些是实际数字
Ignacio finds based on these recorded
伊格纳西奥根据这些记录发现
penalty kicks from the 1417 games okay
1417比赛罚点球好吗
so we do see that there's biases here
所以我们确实看到这里有偏见
there's some advantages and
有一些优势，
disadvantages
缺点
so going left against right is slightly
所以左转右转稍微
better than a four a kicker that going
胜过四踢
right versus left not so different but
右与左没什么不同，但
left left
左左
compared to right right we see a little
与正确的相比，我们看到了一点
bit more of a difference so this is an
有所不同，所以这是一个
asymmetric game it's a fairly subtle one
非对称游戏，这是一个相当微妙的游戏
so we have to see whether or not we're
所以我们必须看看我们是否
going to end up with the Nash
以纳什结束
equilibrium in this game okay so why
在这个游戏中保持平衡，为什么呢？
don't we do the following given those
鉴于这些，我们不执行以下操作
numbers you we can pause the video and
数字，我们可以暂停视频，
solve the game so you can take a look at
解决游戏，让您可以看看
this try and figure out what the
这个尝试找出什么
probabilities that the goalie should go
守门员应该走的概率
left so to say the goalie is going to go
离开，说守门员要走了
left with probability P G the kicker is
PG离开的可能性是
going to go left with probability P sub
将以概率P sub向左走
K solve for P sub G and P sub K with
K求解P sub G和P sub K
this matrix so you're going to put P G
这个矩阵，所以你要把PG
here 1 minus P G here PK here 1 minus P
这里1减去PG这里PK这里1减去P
K here and try and solve for the the
在这里K并尝试解决
mixed strategy Nash equilibrium of this
纳什均衡的混合策略
game so take a few minutes pause the
游戏，所以花几分钟暂停
video try and solve that and then we'll
视频尝试解决该问题，然后我们将
come back and look at what the solution
回来看看解决方案
looks like ok so you've had a chance to
看起来还可以，所以您有机会
look through that now let's see what
现在看一下，让我们看看
actually is happening in the in this
实际上发生在
game so what we need is we need PG to
游戏，所以我们需要的是PG
make the kicker indifferent right so if
使踢球者无动于衷，所以如果
the kicker kicks left we can figure out
踢脚向左踢，我们可以弄清楚
what payoff they get if the kicker goes
如果踢球成功，他们会得到什么回报
right we can figure out what payoff they
是的，我们可以找出他们的收益
get so in particular the goalies
特别是守门员
probability of going left versus right
左移与右移的可能性
must have the kicker indifferent so when
必须对踢脚无动于衷
we look at the kickers payoff from going
我们看一下踢球的收益
left compared to their payoff to going
离开与他们的回报相比
right has to be the same you solve that
权利必须与您解决的问题相同
out and what do you end up with PG is
出来，你最终得到PG是什么
is roughly 5/12 in this case or 0.42 so
在这种情况下大约是5/12或0.42
if we do the same for the kicker going
如果我们对踢脚做同样的事情
left versus the kicker going right you
向左踢，向右踢
can go through that and you know setting
可以经历那件事，你知道设置
the the goalies payoff from going left
守门员从左走的收益
versus right being indifferent what do
与权利漠不关心该做什么
we end up with we end up with PK the
我们最终以PK结束
probability that the kicker goes left is
踢手离开的概率是
point three eight so in terms of what we
指出三点八点
found we found that goalies should go
发现我们发现守门员应该走
left forty two percent of the time that
剩下百分之四十二的时间
leaves them going right fifty eight
让他们向右走58
percent of the time
百分之几的时间
kickers should go left with probability
踢手应该左走
0.38 which then puts them going right
0.38然后使它们正确
with probability 0.62 so we have a
概率为0.62，所以我们有一个
simple prediction based on the actual
基于实际的简单预测
frequencies with which kickers and
踢脚的频率和
goalies score when they go left versus
守门员进左时得分
left right and and so forth so if they
左右，依此类推，如果他们
were doing this facing populations of
这样做是面对
people going left and right and these
人们左右走，这些
are the payoffs then this is how they
是回报，这就是他们的方式
should be behaving okay so what happens
应该表现良好，所以会发生什么
in the data let's take a peek
在数据中，让我们来看看
so the Nash frequencies the goalie going
所以纳什频率守门员走
left forty two percent of the time
剩下42％的时间
goalie should go right fifty eight
守门员应该向右走58
percent of the time kicker should go
踢脚的时间百分比应该走
left thirty eight percent of the time
剩下百分之三十八的时间
kicker should go right sixty-two percent
踢手应该正确百分之六十二
of the time what do they actually do out
他们实际上在做什么
of fourteen hundred and seventeen games
一千一百一十七场比赛
that were recorded so we have a
记录下来，所以我们有一个
non-trivial amount of data here goalies
守门员的大量数据
forty to fifty eight right on the money
四十八到五十八对钱
kickers forty sixty so very very close
踢脚四十，所以非常非常接近
to the 3862 so in fact when we see
到3862，所以事实上，当我们看到
professional soccer players playing and
职业足球运动员和
we look at the payoffs they're getting
我们看看他们得到的回报
they're playing almost exactly the Nash
他们几乎在玩纳什
equilibrium in terms of the mixed
就混合而言均衡
strategy or in this case given this is a
策略或在这种情况下，如果这是一个
zero-sum game this is the same as the
零和博弈与
max min strategies and you know if we
最大最小策略，您知道我们是否
ask a question of exactly how they
问一个问题，他们到底如何
learned to do this it's not necessarily
学会做到这一点，不一定
true that they're sitting down and
没错，他们正在坐下来，
looking at a matrix and calculating
看矩阵并计算
these things direct
这些东西直接
but over time they get it you know they
但是随着时间的流逝，他们知道了
should be indifferent between going left
左移之间应该无动于衷
and right so if the other players are
对，如果其他玩家是
going in one direction or the other too
也朝着一个方向
often and they start adjust they can get
经常，他们开始调整他们可以得到
a better payoff from going one direction
从一个方向获得更好的回报
or the other they'll take advantage of
或其他他们会利用的
that and so things have to adjust and in
所以事情必须调整
keeping them and different overtime so
保持他们和不同的加班时间
you know do players randomize well over
你知道球员们随机分配得很好吗
time yeah pretty well and you know
时间不错，你知道
ignacio's paper goes in much more detail
ignacio的论文更加详细
on this and looks at you know at things
在这，看着你知道的东西
like how well they do in terms of mixing
喜欢他们在混音方面的表现
you know is do they if you wanted to
你知道吗，如果他们愿意的话
make 50/50 one way to do it would be to
使50/50的一种方法是
go left one time then right the next
向左走一次，然后向右走
time then right left the next time and
时间，然后下一次右移，然后
so forth and just alternate that's
等等，只是交替
obviously not randomizing and so instead
显然不是随机的，所以
there's a question of whether people
有一个问题是人们是否
randomize so that they're really
随机化，以便他们真的
unpredictable over time and Ignacio
随着时间的流逝和伊格纳西奥无法预测
finds that they do fairly well even in
发现他们即使在
terms of the strings of kicks that they
他们踢腿的条件
have there's other questions you could
还有其他问题可以
ask you know how well do they perform
问你知道他们的表现如何
under pressure if it's a big game and
如果这是一场大比赛，将面临压力
it's a very important kick do this tend
这是非常重要的一击
to go towards their stronger foot did
走向他们更坚强的脚
they become predictable well you know in
他们变得可以预见，你知道
fact now you see more and more
事实上，现在您看到越来越多
professional sports teams hiring
专业运动队招聘
statisticians hiring game there's
统计学家在招聘游戏
keeping track of exactly what's going on
跟踪到底发生了什么
in terms of other other teams tendencies
就其他球队的倾向而言
whether they tend to do in this
他们是否倾向于这样做
situation what do they tend to do in
他们倾向于在什么情况下做
that situation what's our best strategy
那情况是我们最好的策略
in response to that so you know going
作为回应，所以你知道会
through and analyzing these things has
通过分析这些东西有
become more of a trend in other sports
成为其他运动中的一种趋势
there's similar analyses there's a very
有类似的分析
nice paper by Mark Walker and John Wood
马克·沃克和约翰·伍德的好论文
errs the American Economic Review
犯了《美国经济评论》
looking at tennis and serves so you know
看网球和服务，所以你知道
to which side you have to serve into a
您必须向哪一方服务
given area do you serve towards the left
给定区域，您是否向左服务
side of it the right side of it the
它的右边
center which how does it depend on
中心如何依赖
whether you're right-handed left-handed
无论您是右撇子还是左撇子
which directions you're going in and so
你要去哪个方向等等
forth so they in analyze a series of
因此，他们在分析一系列
professional tennis games and similarly
职业网球比赛
they find that minimax plays is
他们发现minimax玩的是
good predictor of exactly what's going
准确预测即将发生的事情
on and you know there there's also
继续，你知道那里也
questions of how well people really mix
人们如何真正融合的问题
over time but the the the equilibrium
随着时间的流逝，但均衡
predictions do fairly well okay you know
预测效果还不错，你知道
we see there they're gonna be games that
我们看到那里会有游戏
have mixed strategy equilibria in
具有混合策略平衡
particular zero-sum and competitive
特别是零和竞争
games will tend to have them in in a lot
游戏往往会吸引很多人
of situations players have to be
在某些情况下玩家必须
indifferent between what the players
玩家之间无动于衷
they're facing that gives you some very
他们正面临着给你一些
interesting comparative statics you know
您知道的有趣的比较静力学
we asked the question do we really see
我们问了一个问题，我们真的看到了吗
randomization we found you know yes in
随机化我们发现您知道是
professional sports we do see
我们看到的专业运动
randomization there's lots of other
随机化还有很多其他
things in the world where you see
您所看到的世界上的事物
randomization so predator-prey games you
随机，所以捕食者-猎物游戏
know in nature if you come up a Conor
自然知道您是否会提出康纳
squirrel a squirrel thinks you're trying
松鼠认为你在尝试
to catch it what does it do it
抓住它是做什么的
randomizes a bit so it's very
随机化一点，所以非常
unpredictable to figure out which way
无法预测出哪种方式
the squirrel is going to dart when
松鼠飞镖的时候
you're walking by it it's you know it's
你在走，那是你知道的
following essentially a randomized
基本上是随机的
strategy many business interactions so
战略许多业务互动，所以
if we look at things like audits tax
如果我们看看审计税
auditing that's that's a game where
审核那就是游戏
you're going to see a situation where
你会看到一种情况
it's competitive and tax authorities
是竞争和税务机关
don't necessarily want you to know
不一定要你知道
exactly whether you're gonna be audit or
确切地说，您是否要接受审核或
not they want you might want you to have
他们不是想要你可能想要你拥有
some uncertainty so they can't audit
有些不确定性，因此他们无法审核
every if they can't audit everybody in
如果他们不能审核每个人
the population if there's a cost to
人口，如果有成本
auditing that's going to be a game where
审核那将是一场比赛
they're going to mix and that random
他们将混合，随机
randomization might help tax authorities
随机化可能有助于税务机关
so there's a lot of settings where
所以有很多设置
random random checks random audits are
随机随机检查随机审核
essentially optimal strategies as as
基本上是最佳策略
part of some game and we're next Nash
游戏的一部分，我们接下来是纳什
equilibria in particular mixed strategy
均衡特别是混合策略
Nash equilibria will help us understand
纳什均衡将帮助我们理解
those things
那些事